A sound soul, dwells within a sound mind, and a sound body.
Report. What is the status of the moral manipulation machine?
We've just received word from Mosquito who's in charge of the project. It's going well. The prototype is nearing completion.
Are we sure that shriveled insect can handle this? He's shrunken over the last 800 years.
I'm sick of doing nothing. I want some action. Let me go, too.
Your assistance will be unnecessary. I've already employed all the muscle we need.
Muscle? He's a legendary samurai. Perhaps you've heard of him. He's known as the Sword God.
And what would make someone like the Sword God so eager to help us?
Human beings are so very easy to control once you know their weaknesses.
What would make someone like the Sword God so eager to help us?
How would make someone like the Sword God so eager to help us?
Six人目も合わさず運命まで絡んでく
行き先もらったポテル食えない夜を恥で
不可愛しすぎた眩しさが悪い夢に続いても
繋いだ魂の火が胸を刺すなら
言葉よりもっと強い響きが今聞こえるか
やっと理由は途絶びに突きつけられて
触れた瞬間の傷の分だけ確かになれる
Soul, you don't have to feed me.
It's embarrassing.
Don't be so stubborn.
You need to eat more to get your strength back.
The magic should work its way from your body in a few days.
We all heard her, Maka.
Now open up and eat something.
Ta-da!
Nice marker.
Please don't do it.
My autograph will do you a lot more good than any food and medicine will.
Now sit still.
Hey, wait.
No, stop it.
Get off me, Blackstar.
What do you think you're doing?
Well, if you don't have a cast to sign.
As soon as I'm feeling better, you're gonna pay for this, Blackstar.
Finished.
I've arranged all the medicine bottles to be perfectly symmetrical.
You can rest easy now that you don't have to worry about those.
Only you would worry about those.
You've got a lively bunch of visitors, Maka.
What brings you here, Sid?
Nygas, can I speak with you out in the hallway?
Of course.
The Sword God Rises.
Does it have a sweet or a salty taste?
A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
As it has always been.
What's got you so riled up?
Only the reckless will ever completely rid themselves of fear.
Isn't that one of the Academy's teachings?
A fear of disapproval makes one strive to be a good person.
A fear of being powerless gives one the motivation to seek out the power that lies in knowledge.
Fear is a driving force and a creator of order.
Because of this, the amount of fear that exists in the world far exceeds the amount of actual danger that is present.
At all times, there is an excess of fear flowing from every human being.
The DWMA keeps its status by assembling people as capable and talented as you.
People who are driven to seek the power in knowledge.
By doing so, we are following the will of the Almighty God.
If such a God does exist, he is guilty of asking much and offering very little help in return.
We are left to take care of ourselves.
And in light of that, I prefer an offensive position to a defensive one.
As a scientist, don't you feel the same?
Well, Star?
According to Azusa's report, she's located one of the research labs run by Arachnophobia, the witch Arachnase organization.
It seems they're in the process of developing some kind of magic tool.
Our job is to raid the research lab, secure the plans for the tool, determine its purpose, and then destroy it.
Magic tool.
Have you heard of Abon before?
He's known for being a teacher of witches and supposedly the greatest inventor in our world's history.
We aren't sure yet, but it's likely this tool they're constructing follows Abon's design.
We'll know more soon, but we should get going.
Where to?
Azusa will brief us on the location.
Come on.
Right.
Arachnophobia.
They're the ones who hurt Maka.
What's our progress?
Are we getting the expected results?
The prototype has not yet achieved everything we had hoped.
But I'm certain that if we continue our research as planned, Lady Arachnase will be pleased with what we accomplish.
Insanity cannot exist in a moral vacuum.
Some morals must remain in order to give shape to the madness.
That is where our moral manipulation machine comes in.
It will alter people's sense of morality without obliterating it.
Even a slight deterioration will give rise to the madness we seek.
This device, based upon Abon's design, will do much to further Lady Arachnase's plans.
You agreed to be our guard in exchange for the witch's protection, but perhaps you'd like a more permanent position.
No, I'm not interested.
I'm funny!
Protecting Angela is my only concern.
Nothing else matters to me.
What the...
Well done.
Azusa, do you copy?
We reached point B as planned.
No incidents to report so far.
Further instructions?
That was fast.
Hold on for a minute, and I'll put together a map to get you where you need to go.
Resonate with me now.
Audit.
L'ervoyance.
Distance to objective.
32 meters down a hallway that is 3.2 meters wide.
All right, Sid.
I've completed a map of the facility.
Take your next right turn, continuing for 15 meters.
Then proceed up the staircase.
The largest room in that corridor contains your target.
That's a nifty trick.
She's a death scythe.
Of course she's got some cool techniques up her sleeve.
I can only see within a 50-meter range, and I have to maintain my resonance with Sid to do so,
but it comes in handy.
Anything's better than going in blind, right, Sid?
And what's more, we're using a radio as the medium to establish our soul resonance.
Azusa's the only one who can do that.
I appreciate all of the compliments, but back to business.
Right.
What's up ahead?
The signal from the room containing the target is weak.
Still, I am detecting a witch's soul and an old monster's soul.
Oh, and be careful.
There's another very strong soul in there along with them.
Yeah, I'm picking up on those souls as well.
But our assignment is to destroy the magic tool in there.
No matter what.
Intruder alert.
Not good.
We've been detected.
Hurry to the main entrance.
We need to alert the bodyguard.
Why the main entrance?
Hey, Azusa, what's going on?
Hold on.
I'm checking.
This path leads directly to the main entrance.
What's an academy student doing here?
Keep on coming at me.
I'll tear every single one of you into pieces.
My, what a lively young guest we have here.
That girl.
I know her.
Ah, you guys again?
This guy.
It's the samurai Mifune.
Why are you in this place?
Why?
I'm here doing my duty.
My sword is sworn to protect little children like the witch Angela.
But you are also a young child.
Why have you come here?
What are you doing standing against me again?
Is there a problem?
You come with me, Miss Angela.
That's interesting.
Get ready.
Let's go.
Infinite sword attack.
The swords may only be stuck into the ground, but they all radiate danger.
Oh?
A child can withstand Mifune's attack.
Blocking my sword and immediately counter-attacking.
I can tell you've improved.
Maybe I was wrong.
Perhaps you're not a child anymore.
Don't mess with me!
You may know how to talk a big game, but I've beaten you once before and I can do it again.
You didn't beat him, stupid.
Mifune's always nice to kids, no matter what.
He never fights seriously against a dumb little boy like you.
What kind of man is he?
You are not to show any mercy.
Is that understood?
You may be a child, but I won't let myself give in to the same opponent twice.
This is the tour we've heard so much about.
If I had to guess, I'd say it's used to alter human morality.
What's this?
I'll bring it back.
Azusa, what's the situation at the entrance?
The academy student is fighting the strong soul from earlier.
However, the difference in their relative strengths is overwhelming.
This tool needs to be destroyed immediately.
It wasn't part of the plan, but I should be able to take care of this with that student keeping them distracted.
Whoever that is out there will need to take him with us.
I'll just use your own sword against you.
You're still mine!
Three-path shot.
Blackstar!
Go, smoke bomb mode!
Hmm.
A ninja sword.
A kusarigama.
And smoke bomb.
That magic weapon.
Is she...?
Thanks for that, Hibaki.
Now, enchanted sword mode!
Indeed, there's no doubt.
It was Lady Arachne's sister who made that kind of magic weapon.
Rumor has it that one of those weapons joined the DWMA.
It must be her.
Oh.
Let's go!
There's dark energy coming from this sword.
Sabaki!
Yes!
Is that all you can do, enchanted sword?
Please, please!
Infinite sword attack.
One sword.
Two.
Three.
Four swords.
Five.
Six.
Seven swords.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
Eleven.
Twelve swords.
Punishment.
He's striking all of the surrounding swords.
Twenty-four blows total.
Rather effective to use twelve blades against an enemy.
Black Star!
The wounds aren't too deep, but surely you've had enough.
Weapon.
Your name is Tsubaki, right?
Take this child and go.
Why would you waste the skills you have to help a witch?
Damn it!
She calls that not fighting seriously?
Seriously?
Why did you two come here?
Because this lab is run by a witch?
That witch is responsible for hurting our friend.
We came to get revenge.
I'm gonna punish her for what she did to Maka.
No one hurts my friend and gets away with it.
No one.
Do you understand me?
I see.
Sorry about that.
There's no reason for you to apologize.
I know you're a good man at heart.
A sword like yours shouldn't be defending this organization.
You care about helping children and you have incredible skill.
You'd fit in well at the academy.
Why not become a teacher instead?
What?
A teacher at the academy?
You're the best teacher in the academy!
No.
I...
I could never do that.
Mifonic!
It's an impossible dream.
The DWMA despises witches.
I could never bring Angela there.
Who will protect her if I don't?
Hey, boss.
Who's he?
Ah, him?
He's the new bodyguard.
Now that I got Mifune, this whole town is as good as mine.
Hey, mister.
Are you a samurai?
You've got a pretty awesome sword there.
Do you think I could touch it?
Now, now, young master!
No, you can't.
A sword like this is too dangerous for a kid like you.
But I'll tell you what.
Take this sweet instead.
Hey, mister samurai.
Do you like candy?
I don't eat them.
Well, then why do you have them in your pocket?
And do you like candy, kid?
Mm, uh-huh.
That's why I carry them.
Huh?
Hope you're ready, Mifune.
I have an assignment for you.
Some of my boys have managed to track down a certain witch.
What I want you to do is capture that witch and kill her.
You came here to kill me, didn't you?
That's what everybody else wants anyway.
There's always a lot of killing going on around here.
This little girl is the witch?
Where did that traitor run off to?
What was that guy thinking?
If he'd just killed the witch, the payoff would have been huge.
It'll be all right.
They're gone now.
Candy?
It's okay.
Go ahead.
What's wrong with you, Mifune?
Hurry up and finish them off.
Why?
This battle has already been ended.
The DWMA is our staunchest enemy.
There's no reason to let these two live.
If you don't take care of them,
I cannot guarantee the safety of Miss Angela.
Angela.
I'm not done with you yet.
No, don't, Blackstar.
Mifune, isn't this enough?
As a witch, Angela has no chance of living safely among humans.
The protection arachnophobia offers is an invaluable resource.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Mosquito!
Another attack?
Where's it coming from?
Mosquito, there are explosives everywhere.
Get out of here before you're injured.
More blood.
Miss Angela, come this way.
I missed the second shot.
I guess it's not surprising that he's the student who showed up.
It's no big shock to find him here.
Everybody knows how much Blackstar likes to fight.
Never could have hit an enemy that far off without your help.
Thanks, Azusa.
Within ten kilometers, my margin of error is negligible.
That samurai is good, though.
He found us and moved into a blind spot.
As I suspected, he's no ordinary fighter.
Hey, hold it!
Let's finish what we started.
Don't push yourself.
You're strong, I'll give you that.
Keep improving as you have been, and you'll be fine.
Try to understand the other presence within Tsubaki.
The enchanted sword mode will work better for you that way.
I know a lot about swords, and you've got yourself a good one, kid.
Yeah, I know that!
That friend of yours who was hurt by the witch?
See that she gets this.
Well, I think I'm headed home.
You gonna be okay here by yourself?
Yeah, thanks, Sol.
Yo, can I come in?
What now?
Are you gonna sign my face again?
Here, catch!
What is this?
I got it from this soft-hearted samurai I know.
It's just candy.
What's with that guy?
He didn't even apologize for earlier.
Who knows?
I went to that laboratory to get revenge for a friend who got hurt.
And I ended up playing Mifune's damn candy striper.
What kind of sweet is this?
I think that it's seaweed flavor.
A salty one.
There she is.
Okay.
Water.
Oh
How annoying Medusa's coming back next time
Next time the stories about Mifuri taking me to the park. No, Angie, it's not. Please be quiet
But I wanna go to the park. No, listen
I wanna go be a good little girl and listen to your elders
Why should I listen to you? You're still just a kid on the next episode of soul eater
Medusa's revival spider and snakes faithful reunion watch it or I'll take your soul